<resources>

    <string name="privacy_policy_desc">In compliance with what is established in Law 1581 of 2012 and the National Decree number 1377 of 2013, in addition to the constitutional rights, freedoms and guarantees referred to in article 15 of the Political Constitution, and the right to the information established in article 20, in which the general provisions for the protection of personal data are dictated, and due to its high commitment with the protection of personal data, the company COMUNIDAD PRETO S.A.S. (NIT: 901.075.723-7), issues this policy in order to ensure that the personal data provided and authorized by our users, customers, applicants, employees, suppliers, shareholders, and other subjects of the community that interact with the company COMUNIDAD PRETO SAS, henceforth the Users, are stored internally with high security standards that ensure their proper processing and custody.

\n\n<b>1. OBJECTIVE:</b>
\nThe current Data Privacy Policy (henceforth the "Policy") aims to regulate the collection, storage, use, circulation and deletion of personal data in the company COMUNIDAD PRETO SAS (hereafter "THE COMPANY"), providing the tools to ensure the authenticity, confidentiality and integrity of the information.

\n\n<b>2. SCOPE:</b>
\nThis Data Privacy Policy will be applied to all Databases and / or Files containing Personal or Company Data that are subject to Processing by THE COMPANY.

\n\n<b>3. DEFINITIONS: </b>

\n• Authorization: prior, express and informed consent of the Owner to carry out the Processing of Personal Data. 
\n• Privacy Notice: Verbal or written communication generated by the person responsible, addressed to the Owner, for the Processing of his/her Personal Data, which informs about the existence of the Data Privacy Policies that will be applicable to him/her, the means for accessing them and the purposes of the Processing that is intended to be given to personal data.
\n• Database: Organized set of Personal Data that is subject to Processing
\n• Processing: Any operation or set of operations performed on Personal Data, such as collection, storage, use, circulation or deletion.
\n• Client: Natural or juridical person, public or private, with whom THE COMPANY has a business relationship.
\n• User: Natural or juridical person who uses the services offered by THE COMPANY.
\n• Personal Data: Any information linked to or associated with one or more specific or determinable natural persons. Examples of personal data include: name, citizenship card, address, email, telephone number, marital status, health data, fingerprint, salary, property, financial statements, etc.
\n• Sensitive data: understood as the data that affect the privacy of the Owner or which\'s abuse may lead to discrimination, such as those that reveal racial or ethnic origin, political orientation, religious or philosophical beliefs, membership in unions, social organizations, human rights organizations, or that promote the interests of any political party or that ensures the rights and guarantees of opposition political parties, as well as data related to health, sexual life and biometric data.
\n• Owner: Natural person whose Personal Data is subject to Processing.
\n• Entrusted for the Processing: Natural or juridical person, public or private, that by itself or in association with others, performs the Processing of Personal Data on behalf of the one Responsible for the Processing. In the events in which the person Responsible does not act as the one Entrusted for the Processing, the person Entrusted will be specifically identified.
\n• Responsible for the Processing: Natural or juridical person, public or private, that by itself or in association with others, decides on the Database and / or the Processing of the data.
\n• Complaint: Request from the data Owner or from those authorized by him or by law to correct, update or delete his/her personal data or to revoke the authorization in the cases established by law.
\n• Transfer: Data Transfer takes place when the person Responsible for the Processing of personal data, located in Colombia, sends the information or the personal data to a receiver, who in turn is Entrusted for the Processing and is within or outside the country.
\n• Transmission: Processing of Personal Data that involves its communication within or outside the Colombian territory, when it is intended to conduct a Processing by the person Entrusted on behalf of the person Responsible.


\n\n<b>4. RIGHTS OF THE HOLDERS:</b>

\n\nThe Owner of the personal data will have the following rights:
\nA) To know, update and rectify their personal data from who is Responsible or Entrusted of the Processing. This right may be exercised, among others, for partial, inaccurate, incomplete, fractioned or misleading data, or that which\'s Processing is expressly prohibited or has not been authorized;
\nB) Request proof of the authorization that was granted to the Person Responsible for Processing, except when it is expressly excepted as a requirement for Processing, in accordance with the provisions of article 5 of this document
\nC) To be informed by the Responsible or the Entrusted of the Handling, upon request, about the use that has been given to the personal data;
\nD) Submit to the Superintendence of Industry and Commerce complaints for violations of the provisions of this policy and other regulations that modify, add or compliment it;
\nE) To revoke the authorization and / or to request the suppression of the data when the principles, rights and constitutional and legal guarantees are not respected during the Handling of the information. The revocation and / or suppression shall proceed when the Superintendence of Industry and Commerce has determined that, in the Handling of the information, that who is Responsible or Entrusted to do so has engaged in conducts against this policy and the Constitution;
\nF) Have free access to his own personal data, which has been handled by the following people.
\n• By the Owner;
\n• By those assigned, who must prove such quality;
\n• By the representative and / or proxy of the Owner, after accrediting the representation;
\n• By stipulation in favor of or for another



\n\n<b>5. PROCESSING AND PURPOSES TO WHICH THE PERSONAL DATA WILL BE SUBJECT TO </b>

\n\nTHE COMPANY, acting as Responsible for the Processing of Personal Data, with the purpose of ensuring the proper development of its commercial activities, as well as for the strengthening of its relations with third parties, collects, stores, uses, circulates and suppresses Personal Data corresponding to natural persons or legal entities, with which it has or has had a relationship, such as, but not limited to, workers and their families, shareholders, consumers, customers, distributors, suppliers, creditors and debtors, for the following purposes:

\n\n<b>a. General purposes for the Processing of Personal Data: </b>

\n\n• Allow the owner\'s participation in marketing and promotional activities (including participation in contests, raffles and sweepstakes) made by THE COMPANY;
\n• Evaluate the quality of the service, conduct market studies on consumer habits, statistical analysis and others that allow us to understand our users in order to improve services and processes and for internal uses;
\n• Control access to the COMPANY\'s platforms;
\n• Control access to COMPANY\'s work sites and establish security measures, including the establishment of video-surveillance zones;
\n• To respond to queries, comments, petitions, complaints and claims made by the owners or control entities and transmit the Personal Data to the other authorities, who under the applicable law, must receive the Personal Data;
\n• In order to be able to contact, by e-mail, or by any other means, those who have or have had a relationship, such as, but without limitation to, employees and their families, shareholders, users, customers, distributors, suppliers, creditors and debtors, for the purposes previously mentioned;
\n• Transfer the information collected to different areas of THE COMPANY;
\n• To attend legal or administrative requirements and to fulfill judicial or legal mandates;
\n• To register your personal data in the COMPANY\'S information systems and its commercial and operational databases;
\n• Any other activities of a nature similar to those described above that are necessary to carry out the COMPANY\'S corporate purpose of THE COMPANY.

\n\n<b>b. Regarding the personal data of our Clients and Users: </b>

\n\n• To fulfill the obligations contracted by THE COMPANY with its Customers.
\n• Send information about changes in the services or conditions.
\n• Send information about offers related to the products or services offered by THE COMPANY or its related companies;
\n• Facilitate communication between the COMPANY\'S Clients and Users
\n• To strengthen relationships with its Users and Clients, by sending relevant information, taking orders and evaluating the quality of the service;
\n• For determining outstanding obligations, consult financial information and credit history and for the reporting of unfulfilled obligations with respects to its debtors to Credit Reporting Agencies.
\n• To improve, promote and develop its products and those of its related companies worldwide;
\n• To allow the companies who are linked to THE COMPANY, with whom it has executed contracts which include provisions to guarantee the security and the appropriate treatment of the personal data processed, to contact the Holder for the purpose of offering goods or services of interest;
\n• Use the different services through the websites, mobile applications or other tools of THE COMPANY, including downloads of contents and formats.

\n\n<b>C. Regarding the Data of Suppliers:</b>

\n\n• To invite them to participate in selection processes and to events organized or sponsored by THE COMPANY;
\n• To evaluate the fulfillment of their obligations;
\n• To register on the COMPANY\'S systems;
\n• To process their payments and verify outstanding balances;


\n\n<b>6. PRINCIPLES APPLICABLE TO THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA</b>

\n\nFor the Treatment of Personal Data, THE COMPANY shall apply the following principles, which are the rules to be followed in the collection, handling, use, treatment, storage and exchange of Personal Data:

\n\n• Legality: The processing of personal data will be carried out in accordance with applicable legal provisions (Statutory Law 1581 of 2012 and its regulatory decrees).
\n• Purpose: The Treatment must obey a legitimate purpose in accordance with the Constitution and the Law, which must be informed to the Owner.
\n• Freedom: The collection of Personal Data may only be exercised with the previous, express and informed authorization from the Owner.
\n• Accuracy or Quality: The information subject to the Processing of Personal Data must be truthful, complete, accurate, updated, verifiable and understandable.
\n• Transparency: The Processing of Personal Data guarantees the right of the Owner to obtain at any time and without restrictions, information about the existence of data that concerns him or her.
\n• Restricted access and circulation: The processing of personal data can only be done by the persons authorized by the Owner and / or by those established in the Law.
\n• Security: The Personal Data subject to Processing must be handled with the technical, human and administrative measures necessary to provide security for the records, avoiding their adulteration, loss, consultation, use or unauthorized or fraudulent access
\n• Confidentiality: All employees working in THE COMPANY are obliged to maintain confidentiality of the personal information they have access to during their work in THE COMPANY.

\n\n<b>7. DUTIES OF THE COMPANY AS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA:</b>

\n\nTHE COMPANY knows that the Personal Data is owned by the persons to which they refer to and only they can decide on them. In that sense, THE COMPANY will use the Personal Data collected solely for the purposes for which it is duly authorized and respecting, in any case, the current regulations on the Protection of Personal Data
\n\n<b>8. AUTHORIZATION: </b>

\n\nTHE COMPANY will request previous, express and informed consent from the Owners of the Personal Data which it requires to Process.

\n\nThis manifest of the will of the Owner may occur through different mechanisms made available by THE COMPANY, such as:
\n• Acceptance on the COMPANY\'S platforms
\n• In writing, filling out an authorization format for the Processing of Personal Data determined by THE COMPANY.
\n• Orally, through a telephone conversation or videoconference.
\n• By means of unequivocal conducts which allows to conclude that it has granted its authorization, through its express acceptance to the Terms and Conditions of an activity within which the authorization of the participants is required for the Processing of their Personal Data.

\n\nImportant: In no case will THE COMPANY assimilate the silence of the Owner to an unequivocal conduct.

\n\n<b>9. SPECIAL PROVISIONS FOR THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA:</b>

\n\n<b>a. Sensitive Data Processing: </b>

\n\nThe Processing of Personal Data which is of sensitive nature is prohibited by law, unless there is a previous, express and informed authorization from the Owner, among other exceptions established in Article 6 of Law 1581 of 2012.
\nIn this case, in addition to complying with the requirements established for the authorization, THE COMPANY will inform the Owner:
\n• that due to its sensitive nature, the Owner is not obliged to authorize its Processing
\n• which of the data that will be subject to Processing are sensitive and the purpose of their Processing.

\n\nIn addition, THE COMPANY will treat the sensitive data collected under security and confidentiality standards corresponding to its nature. To this end, THE COMPANY has implemented administrative, technical and legal measures which are mandatory for its employees and in turn applicable to its suppliers, related companies and commercial allies.

\n\n<b>b. Treatment of Personal Data of Children and Adolescents: </b>

\n\nAccording to the provisions in Article 7 of Law 1581 of 2012 and article 12 of Decree 1377 of 2013, THE COMPANY will only carry out the Processing of data corresponding to children and adolescents, provided that this Processing responds to and respects the best interests of Children and adolescents and ensures respect for their fundamental rights.

\n\n<b>10. PROCEDURE FOR THE RESPONSE TO PETITIONS, CONSULTATIONS, COMPLAINTS AND CLAIMS OF PERSONAL DATA OWNERS:</b>

\n\nThe Owners of Personal Data processed by THE COMPANY have the right to access their Personal Data and the details of such processing, as well as to rectify and update them in case they are inaccurate, or to request its elimination when they consider that they are excessive or unnecessary for the purposes for which they were obtained, or oppose to their processing for specific purposes.
\nThe means that have been implemented to guarantee the exercise of these rights through the presentation of the respective request are:
\n• Communication directly with COMUNIDAD PRETO S.A.S using the electronic means established in the platforms of COMUNIDAD PRETO
\n• Request presented through the contact telephone numbers established in the platforms of COMUNIDAD PRETO.
\nThese channels may be used by personal data owners, or third parties authorized by law to act on their behalf, for the purpose of exercising the following rights:

\n\n<b>a. Procedure for presenting requests and queries:</b>

\n\n• The Owner may consult his/her personal data at any time. For this purpose, you may submit a request indicating the information you wish to know, through any of the mechanisms mentioned above.
\n• The Owner or those assigned by him must prove their identity, that of his representative, the representation or stipulation in favor of another. When the request is made by a person other than the Owner and does not prove that it is acting on behalf of the Owner, the request shall be deemed as not submitted.
\n• The query and / or request must contain at least the name and contact address of the Owner or any other means to receive the response, as well as a clear and precise description of the personal data in respect to which the Owner seeks to exercise the right to Consultation and / or request.

\n\n<b>b. Procedure for presenting complaints: </b>
\nIn accordance with the provisions of Article 14 of Law 1581 of 2012, when the Owner or that assigned by him, consider that the information processed by THE COMPANY must be corrected, updated or deleted, or when it must be revoked because of the alleged non-compliance of any of the duties contained in the Law, they may submit a request to THE COMPANY, which will be processed under the following rules:  
        \n\ni) The Owner or those assigned by him must prove their identity, that of his representative, the representation or stipulation in favor of another. When the request is made by a person other than the Owner and does not prove that it is acting on behalf of the Owner, the request shall be deemed as not submitted.
\n(ii) The request for rectification, updating, deletion or revocation must be submitted through the means authorized by THE COMPANY indicated in this document and it must contain at least the following information: 
        \n• The name, email address, address of the Owner or any other means to receive the response. 
        \n• Documents that prove the identity of the applicant and, if appropriate, that of his representative with the respective authorization. 
        \n• The clear and precise description of the personal data over which the Owner seeks to exercise any of the rights and the specific request.

        \n\n<b>11. PASSIVELY OBTAINED INFORMATION: </b>
        \n\n  When using the services contained within the COMPANY\'S platforms, the COMPANY may collect information in a passive way through information management technologies, such as "cookies", through which information about the hardware and the computer software, IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access time and the addresses of the origin websites, among others, is collected; Personal Data of the users is not collected directly through the use of these tools. Information about the pages that the person visits most frequently on these websites will also be collected in order to understand their browsing habits. Nevertheless, the user of the COMPANY\'S websites has the possibility to configure the operation of the "cookies", according to the options of his internet browser.
        \n\n<b>  12. SAFETY OF PERSONAL DATA:   </b>
       \n\n THE COMPANY, in strict application of the Security Principles for the Processing of Personal Data, shall provide the technical, human and administrative measures necessary to provide security to the records, avoiding their unauthorized adulteration, loss, consultation, use or fraudulent access. The COMPANY\'s obligation and responsibility is limited to having adequate means for this purpose. THE COMPANY does not guarantee the total security of its information nor is it liable for any consequences resulting from technical failures or improper entry by third parties to the Database or file containing the Personal Data subject to Processing by the COMPANY those Entrusted by it. THE COMPANY will require its service providers to contract, adopt and comply with appropriate technical, human and administrative measures for the protection of the Personal Data these suppliers are entrusted of.    
       \n\n<b> 13. TRANSFER, TRANSMISSION AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA   </b>
        \n\nTHE COMPANY may disclose the Personal Data to third parties not related to THE COMPANY when: 
        \n• They are contractors in execution of contracts for the development of the activities of THE COMPANY; 
        \n• Transfer by any title of any business line to which the information relates  

        \n\nIn any case, when THE COMPANY wishes to send or transmit data to one or more Entrusted entities located within or outside the territory of Colombia, it shall establish contractual clauses or subscribe a contract for the transmission of personal data in which the following provisions are established, among others:  
        \n(i) The scope and purpose of the Processing. 
        \n(ii) The activities that the one Entrusted will carry out on behalf of THE COMPANY. 
        \n(iii) The obligations that the one Entrusted must comply with in respect to the Data Owner and THE COMPANY. 
        \n(iv) The obligation of the Data Processor to treat the data in accordance with the purpose authorized for it and complying with the principles established in the Colombian Law and the present policy. 
        \n(v) The obligation of that Entrusted to adequately protect personal data and databases, as well as to maintain confidentiality regarding the processing of transmitted data.  

        \n\nTHE COMPANY will not request authorization when the international transfer of data is covered by any of the exceptions provided for in the Law and its Regulatory Decrees.  

        \n\n<b>14. APPLICABLE LEGISLATION:  </b>
        \n\nThis Personal Data Protection Policy, the Privacy Notice, and the Authorization Form that is part of this Policy, are governed by the provisions in the current legislation on the protection of Personal Data referred to in Article 15 Of the Political Constitution of Colombia, Law 1266 of 2008, Law 1581 of 2012, Decree 1377 of 2013, Decree 1727 of 2009 and other norms that modify, revoke or replace them.  
        \n\n<b>15. EFFECTIVENESS: </b>
        \n\n  This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 1, 2017.  
</string>

</resources>
