<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="terms_condition">

<b>1. OWNERSHIP: </b>
\n\nCOMUNIDAD PRETO S.A.S. is a Company constituted according to Colombian laws, identified with NIT 901.075.723-7, established in the city of Medellin, which for the present purposes will be called THE COMPANY.

<b>2. DEFINITIONS: </b>
\n\n<b>Platforms:</b> all the technological platforms related to Preto, including the Preto mobile app, the webpage www.preto.co, or any other software related to Preto existing today or in the future.
\n\n<b>User:</b>  any person or company that accesses and uses the platforms and/or services offered by THE COMPANY.
\n\n<b>Offeror: </b> any person or Company who offers their products or services through any of the Preto Platforms.

\n\n<b>Las Plataformas:</b> todas las plataformas tecnológicas relacionadas con Preto, incluyendo la aplicación móvil Preto, el sitio web www.preto.co o cualquier otro software relacionado con Preto, existentes ahora o en el futuro.
\n<b>Usuario:</b> Persona natural o jurídica que accede o hace uso de las Plataformas y/o de los servicios ofrecidos por LA COMPAÑÍA.
\n<b>Oferente:</b> Persona natural o jurídica que ofrece sus productos o servicios a través de cualquiera de Las Plataformas Preto.

\n\n<b>3. LEGAL NATURE: </b>
\n\nThese terms and conditions regulate the contractual relationship of commercial nature that binds the Users, who access and/or use the Platforms, and THE COMPANY, especially in the authorization of use that it grants in favor of these, and are established with the aim of communicating the rights and responsibilities of each one.

\n\nBy accessing and/or using the Platforms, you as a user agree with these terms and conditions.

\n\n<b>4. GENERAL CONSIDERATIONS:</b>
\n\nThe services provided by the Platforms are for personal use.
\nThe products and services offered through the Platforms are only available for the users who, according to the current Colombian legislation, have the legal capacity to contract. The users who are not in this capacity should refrain from using the services of the virtual store.
\nIt is the user\'s obligation to download the proper version for their device. In order to install, make use and ensure the proper operation of the Platforms you may need to install updates or upgrades to the software in order to continue accessing and using the Platforms or parts of it.

\nThe services are provided by the Platforms through a technology platform license and electronic commerce logistics services.

\n\n<b>5. SECURITY:</b>
\n\nTHE COMPANY has implemented the electronic and administrative procedures to protect and help prevent unauthorized access, avoid loss, misuse, alteration and theft of personal data.
\nThe terms and conditions herein established and the conflicts that may arise regarding their interpretation, use, scope and termination are governed by Colombian law and are subject to Colombian judges and tribunals.

\n\n<b>6. LIMITED RESPONSIBILITY: </b>

\n\nTHE COMPANY is not responsible for the reliability and/or quality of the products or services provided by the Offerors who publish their information in the Platforms, as well as delays, non – compliance and other aspects of the food service they provide.

\n\nNotwithstanding the provisions of applicable Colombian law, THE COMPANY shall not be responsible in any way for any damages suffered as a result of any virus that may have infected the computer or other devices owned by the Users caused by the access, use or download of any material in the Platforms.  If you choose to download material from the Platforms, that action is done at your own risk.

\n\n<b>7. ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS AND TIMELINESS OF INFORMATION: </b>

\n\nThe content that is available in the Platforms is for informational purposes only.
\nAlthough we implement all the means at our disposal to ensure the accuracy and completeness of the information contained in the Platforms, we do not assume any responsibility in the event that the information that is available through these is not accurate or complete. Any modifications you make to the material available in the Platforms will be done at your own risk. You also accept that it will be your responsibility to check any possible changes that may occur. THE COMPANY reserves the right to make changes or corrections to any part of the information available on the Platforms without prior notice.

\n\n<b>8. USE OF THE INFORMATION: </b>
\n\nThe right to privacy is very important for THE COMPANY. To protect that right, the handling of the information of the Users and Offerors is governed by our Privacy Policy, to which you have access.
\nThe Users information gathered from The Platforms can be used to facilitate communication between those who offer their products or services and the user; to answer questions and comments sent; to understand our users and improve services and processes; to send them information that may be of interest; to send them announcements that may be relevant, to administer contests and sweepstakes; to notify of changes in services; to show ads to target audiences of our advertisers.
\nIn some cases the information is used to communicate with the User, in order to respond to their concerns, comments or to address any need regarding information or services.
\nThe data is used for the future sending of information of interest through email, if authorization is granted to THE COMPANY
\nIf you want to offer your products through the Platforms, you can contact THE COMPANY, using the contact button available in the mobile app or the website www.preto.co.
\nIf you wish to send a comment about the Platforms or the information it presents, you can do so using the means intended for this purpose in the mobile app or the website.

\n\n<b>9. INTELECTUAL PROPERTY: </b>

\n\nAll contents, trademarks, logos, drawings, documentation, computer programs or any other element susceptible of protection by the Colombian legislation of intellectual or industrial property, that are accessible through the Platforms, correspond exclusively to THE COMPANY or to its legitimate owners and all rights are expressly reserved over them.
\nIt is expressly prohibited to create hyperlinks to any element of the Platforms without the authorization of THE COMPANY, provided they are not to a web page that does not require identification or authentication for access, or which is restricted.
\nIn any case, THE COMPANY reserves all rights over the contents, information, data and services that it has over them.
\nThe Platforms do not grant the Users any license or authorization of use over its contents, data or services, other than the one expressly detailed in the present general conditions of use.

\n\n<b>10. MODIFICATIONS TO THESE TERMS: </b>

\n\nWe reserve the right, in our sole and complete discretion, to alter these terms and conditions at any time, by showing the new terms and conditions in any of the Platforms. It is your responsibility to periodically check any changes we may make to these terms and conditions. Your continued use of the Platforms, following the publication of the new terms and conditions, will imply and signify your acceptance of the modifications made.

\n\n<b>11. USER OBLIGATIONS: </b>

\n\nBy accepting the present terms, the user complies to:

\n\nProvide accurate and reliable information when creating your User Account
\nRefrain from transferring the validation data to third parties (username and password)
\nRefrain from using the Platforms to carry out acts attempting against morality, public order and good customs towards THE COMPANY, the Offerors or third parties
\nImmediately inform THE COMPANY in case of forgetting or usurpation of the validation data.  You are responsible for all the activities that occur in your account.
\nRefrain from conducts that threatens the functioning of the Platforms
\nRefrain from stealing the identify of other Users
\nRefrain from decrypting, decompiling or disassembling any element of the Platforms or any part of it.
\nRefrain from impersonating another user, create or use an account for anyone other than you, provide an email address other than your own, create multiple accounts or provide false information.
\nIn general all behaviors necessary for the execution of the legal business.

\n\n<b>12. COMPANY OBLIGATIONS: </b>

\n\nTHE COMPANY, in virtue of the present terms and in accordance with the information provided by the Offerors, complies to:

\nProvide truthful, reliable, sufficient, clear and updated information regarding what it displays;
\nIndicate the general characteristics to serve as a reference for the Users
\nMake available to the Users the updated terms and conditions for the use of the Platforms
\nUse the information only for the purposes established in these terms

\n\n<b>13. WARRANTY: </b>

\n\nThe User understands and accepts that the consumer relationship is generated directly with the offerors, ie, the people who offer their products and services through the Platforms, therefore, any claims for warranties must be made directly to the offerors, who have the obligation to comply with the claims in the terms defined in Law 1480 of 2011

\n\n<b>14. CONTENT: </b>

\n\nTHE COMPANY may make available to the Users, using the Platforms, commercial and advertising information, own or related to third parties, in accordance with good commercial practices.  In these cases THE COMPANY does not endorse, guarantee or compromise its responsibility towards the services and / or products that are commercialized by these third parties, since the Platforms serve as a means of communication and advertising and not as a tool for providing services; therefore, it is the user\'s complete responsibility to access the sites indicated by advertisements, assuming the obligation to verify and know the terms of the services offered by the third parties.

\n\nAll information made available on the Platforms such as images, advertisements, names, brands, slogans and other elements of intellectual property, are legitimately used by THE COMPANY either because they are of their ownership, because they are authorized to make them available or because they are able to do so in virtue of decisions number 351 from 1993 and 485 from 2000 of the Andean Community of Nations, or in virtue of law 23 from 1982.

\n\n<b>15. FUNCTIONING OF THE PLATFORMS: </b>

\n\nTHE COMPANY operates, directly or through third parties, the Platforms; all the information that is communicated through these corresponds to true and updated information, according to the information provided by the Offerors.  In no case will it be responsible for direct or indirect damages suffered by the User due to the use or inability to use the Platforms.
\nThe Platforms are available 24 hours a day for access.  The COMPANY makes the best efforts to keep the Platforms in operation, but in any case guarantees their availability and permanent continuity.

\n\n<b>16. CANCELATION: </b>

\n\nTHE COMPANY reserves the right to cancel any User accounts and / or to prohibit access to the Platforms to Users that engage in conducts which violate these terms or that do not comply with the contacted obligations.

\n\n<b>17. ELECTRONIC COMMERCE: </b>

\n\nIn compliance with the Colombian provisions on data messages according to Law 527 of 1999, it is reported that national legislation recognizes the validity of data messages and therefore these acquire evidentiary character and entity.  Consequently, Users understand that, through the sending and receiving of data messages, the involved parties can create, modify or terminate obligations, obligations, being exclusively responsible for the content, consequences, responsibilities and effects of the information generated.

\n\n<b>18. TOTAL ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS: </b>

\n\nThe User expressly manifests to have the legal capacity to use the Platform; likewise, it states to have provided real, truthful and reliable information; therefore,

\n\nThe User explicitly expresses the legal capacity to use the Platform; Likewise, it states that it has provided real, truthful and reliable information; therfore declares expressly and unmistakably, that it has read, understands and accepts all the situations regulated in the present writing of terms and conditions for the use of the Platforms, which is why it is committed to the total fulfillment of the duties, obligations, actions and omissions here expressed.
\nIn case Users from other countries use the Platforms, they are fully subject to the provisions of these terms.</string>

</resources>